export const animalData = [
  {
    "question": "What marine animal is known to have three hearts and blue blood?",
    "options": [
      "Shark",
      "Dolphin",
      "Octopus",
      "Jellyfish"
    ],
    "answer": "Octopus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which large flightless bird is native to Australia and is one of the world's fastest runners?",
    "options": [
      "Ostrich",
      "Rhea",
      "Cassowary",
      "Emu"
    ],
    "answer": "Emu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a group of lions called?",
    "options": [
      "Herd",
      "Pack",
      "Pride",
      "Colony"
    ],
    "answer": "Pride"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mammal is the largest on Earth?",
    "options": [
      "African Elephant",
      "Blue Whale",
      "Giraffe",
      "Polar Bear"
    ],
    "answer": "Blue Whale"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which reptile can change its skin color to blend in with its surroundings?",
    "options": [
      "Snake",
      "Crocodile",
      "Iguana",
      "Chameleon"
    ],
    "answer": "Chameleon"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the process called when a caterpillar transforms into a butterfly?",
    "options": [
      "Metabolism",
      "Metamorphosis",
      "Respiration",
      "Hibernation"
    ],
    "answer": "Metamorphosis"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of animal is a King Cobra?",
    "options": [
      "Lizard",
      "Snake",
      "Amphibian",
      "Bird"
    ],
    "answer": "Snake"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal is famous for its slow movement and spending most of its life hanging upside down in trees?",
    "options": [
      "Koala",
      "Sloth",
      "Gibbon",
      "Panda"
    ],
    "answer": "Sloth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which North American bird is known for its ability to mimic the calls of many other birds?",
    "options": [
      "Cardinal",
      "Robin",
      "Blue Jay",
      "Mockingbird"
    ],
    "answer": "Mockingbird"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Giant Panda's diet consists almost entirely of what plant?",
    "options": [
      "Eucalyptus",
      "Bamboo",
      "Grass",
      "Ferns"
    ],
    "answer": "Bamboo"
  }
]